[MUSIC PLAYING]
嘿 各位
Hey, everyone.
大家好
What's up?
我是 Rob Doson
It's Rob Dodson.
欢迎收看 polycast 进阶教程系列的第一期
Welcome to the very first update episode of Polycast.
在这系列的视频中  我将会回到
In these videos, I'm going to go back in time
以前的视频  并且深入挖掘一些及技巧
and dig up some of our older episodes
以便把它们升级成 Polymer 1.0 版相关内容
so I can update them with all the Polymer 1.0 goodness.
今天  我们从 core-icons 上的
Today, we are starting with Polycast numero
Polycast 1.0 开始
uno, which is on core-icons.
那么我将会给各位展示如何使用
So I'm going to show you how to work
全新的 iron-icon 元素
with the new iron-icon element.
大家拭目以待
Let's take a look.
那么今天  我会帮助各位把之前的讲解视频中使用
So today, I'm going to help you convert the previous episode,
core-icon 元素的技巧  转换成
which worked with the core-icon element,
当今 Polymer 1.0 里全新模块的升级版 iron-icon 的使用办法
to the updated iron-icon that is now part of Polymer 1.0.
许多之前在 core 设置中的元素
Many of the elements that were previously in the core set
如今已经被转移到了 iron 设置或者 paper 设置中
have now been ported to either the iron set or the paper set.
我经常放在首位的通用经验法则是
And the general rule of thumb that I like to keep in my head
如果之前的元素大部分只是特性
is if the previous element was mostly just behavior,
那么它们很可能就被转移到了 iron 元素集合中
then it has probably been moved to the iron element set.
如果它有一些用户界面  比如 core 工具栏
If it had a bit of UI to it, like perhaps the core toolbar
或者是 core 头文件板  任何可视化的东西
or the core header panel, anything that's sort of visual,
那么它就会被转移到 paper 集合中
then it has been moved to the paper element set.
现在我们要使用 iron-icon
So we're going to be working with iron-icon today.
首先我们要做的事情
The first thing we're going to do
就是浏览 elements.polymerproject.org 下的目录文件
is go over to the catalog at elements.polymerproject.org
然后继续点击 Iron Element 集合
and go and click on the Iron Elements set
来打开文件
to get the documentation.
然后我就能在这里找到 iron-icon
And I'll just find the docs for the iron-icon element
元素的文件了
inside of here.
如果你看过之前的教学视频  也许你会注意到
And you'll notice that if you've watched the previous episode,
这里的很多文件跟之前完全一样
a lot of these things are the same from before.
如果你使用源文件
We've still got a Source attribute
那么我们依然能得到源属性
if you're working with sources.
而如果你直接对图标进行操作
If you are working directly with an icon,
你得到的也是图标属性
there is still the Icon attribute.
这与之前视频中相似的
So many of the things are similar
地方如此之多
from the previous video.
我想在这里指出的一件事
The one thing that I do want to point out here
你可以在页面的下方看见它
is a little bit further down the page.
你能看到样式的部分
You'll see a section on styling.
这就提到了通过使用自定义属性
And this is going to mention styling
来设置风格样式
using custom properties.
现在 也许你对自定义属性并不熟悉
Now, if you're not familiar with custom properties,
我们在之前的一集视频中详细讲解了
we covered those in a previous episode.
所以如果你回头温习一下
So if you go check out this episode,
就能理解自定义属性是如何起作用的
it will explain how custom properties work.
我的建议是在继续观看本期视频之前
I recommend you go and watch that
先回头看看那一期
before watching the rest of this episode
因为我们在这里需要用到一些自定义属性
because we're going to use these in a little bit.
好了
OK.
现在  为了在我的应用中安装这些
Now, to install these in my application,
我就跳过细节直到重点了
I'm going to hop over into my terminal.
然后我运行 bower 安装  保存
And I will run bower install, save.
你会注意到我也是从 Polymer elements / iron-icons
And you'll notice here that I'm installing from Polymer
目录安装的
elements/iron-icons.
所有的 Polymer 元素设置及其相关内容
All of the Polymer element sets or whatever now
保存在了 GitHub 上的 Polymer elements org
live in this Polymer elements org on GitHub.
所以无论何时  只要你在 bower 安装
So any time you're bower installing,
你就在从 Polymer Elements 调用它
you're doing it from Polymer elements.
这就会溢出并触发回收机制
That's going to go out and fetch the repo,
并将之下载到我的应用中
download it to my application.
那么我准备好进行下一步了
So I'm ready to rock.
现在如果我在 Sublime 中打开工程
Now if I open my project up in Sublime,
其实我打开的是之前视频中创建的老工程
I've actually got the old project from the old episode.
然后我们来把它过一遍并且稍微升级一下
And we're going to go through and update this.
我先打开 bower 组件目录
So I open up my Bower components directory.
你能看到在目录里的这个位置
And you'll see that inside of here,
我们不仅找到了 iron-icon 元素
we've got both the iron-icon element, as well as
而且找到了 iron-icons 元素
the iron-icons element.
所以说借助安装 iron-icons 我也得到了免费的  iron-icon
So by installing iron-icons, I got iron-icon for free
这是因为前者运行依赖于后者
because it depends on it.
接下来  我要打开 HTML 文件索引
Next, I'm going to open my index HTML file.
然后页面向下滚动到这里
And scrolling down here, I'm going
我要替换原来的 polyfills
to replace the old polyfills.
在这个节点上来说这些文件都是相当老旧了
These are quite old at this point.
所以我们要将他们升级来使用 webcomponents-lite.js.
So we're going to update them to use webcomponents-lite.js.
那就是我们在 polymer 1.0 中使用的 polyfi ll 集
That is the polyfill set we use in Polymer 1.0.
然后接下来我们要导入的
And then instead of importing core-icons,
并非是 iron-icons 而是 core-icons
we will import iron-icons.
这就既会导入默认的图标集合
And that is going to import both the default icon set, as well
也能导入 iron-icon 元素
as the iron-icon element.
所以我能使用默认的集合
So I can use that default set.
现在 接下来我想做的事情就是
Now, the next thing I want to do is
页面下提到 core-icons 的这个位置
go down here to where it says core-icon
并将之替换为我个人的 iron-icons
and replace these with my individual iron-icons.
那么我只需要继续删除所有的这些
So I can just go and delete all these.
我们要用到完全相同的图标
We're going to use the same icon.
我们将用到那些安卓的图标
We'll use that android icon.
但是这次  我们将用到 iron-icon 元素来完成
But this time, we'll use the iron-icon element to do it.
这么说来 iron-icon 的图标和安卓的等同  对吧
So iron-icon, icon equals android, right?
相当直截了当
Pretty straightforward.
我可以直接启动一个本地服务器
I can go boot up a local server.
然后我快速上滑到这里  你就能看到
And then I'll zoom in here, and you
显示出来的安卓图标
can see that we've got our Android icon displaying.
然后这里就设置好了
So we're all good there.
好了
OK.
所以如果你想要添加一些额外的图标到你的应用
So if you go to the Element catalog
并查看这些图标
because you want to add some additional icons
是从哪里调用的话
to your application and you want to look up what they're called,
逻辑上讲  你需要转到
logically, you're going to go and look
iron-icons 集合文件来查看
for the iron-icons element set docs.
并且找到一个空白的页面
And what you're going to find is a blank page
因为现在在目录里有一个 BUG
because there is a bug in the catalog right now.
那么我知道这个特殊的 URL 基本上就是说你从目录里的其他地方
So I know about this little special URL, which is basically
获取一个 demo 文件  然后就
you take a demo file from somewhere else in the catalog,
将这个 URL 替换为 iron-icons
and then you just replace the URL with iron-icons.
实际上这操作会为你加载
And that's actually going to load
文件中的 iron-icons
in the docs for your iron-icons for you.
高端的操作吧
It's a total hack.
为了使各位学习更简单  我会给大家一些注释
To make your life easier, I will give you a little annotation
点击这里就可以看见
here that you can click on.
这回直接带你到图标设置
So this will take you right to the icon docs.
这是我们在目录中已经打开过的一个 BUG
This is a bug that we have open in the catalog.
很快这个 BUG 就能得到修复
We're going to get it fixed really soon.
如果你是在本视频拍摄过后很久观看
If you're watching this in the future,
很可能这个 BUG 已经被修复了
maybe it's already fixed.
然而如果你是在今天观看
But if you're watching this today,
并且你想要阅读这些文件  点击注释即可
and you want to read the docs, click that annotation.
这能使你避免一些麻烦
It'll save you a little bit of a headache there.
现在  一旦我直接点击那 URL 我就能看到完整的
Now, once I hit that URL, I'm going to see the full default
默认元素集
elements set.
以上就是我在我的 iron-icons 导入的全部内容
So this is everything that I got in my iron-icons import.
如果我向下滚动鼠标  还能看到其他的我能在
And if I scroll down, there are actually other element sets
我的应用中用到的元素集合
as well that I could use in my application.
比如这个的名为 AV 的用于 audiovisual 图标
So here's one called AV for audiovisual icons.
继续查看  我还在这里看到
And looking around, I can see that this AV snooze
AV snooze 插件的图标  就在这里  看上去很整洁
icon down here, right about here, looks pretty neat.
对吧
Right?
可能我想在我的应用中用到
So maybe I want to use that in my application.
然后我转回我的工程
So I'll hop back into my project.
你能看到当我打开 iron-icon 集合的时候
And you'll see that when I open up the iron-icons set,
就在这个里面  有一点不同的图标设置
that inside of here, there's a few different icon sets.
那儿就是 AV 图标
There are the AV icons.
所以我需要做的就是导入那元素集
So I just need to import that element set.
那么我就在我拖入这些 iron icons 之后点击导入
So I will drop an import after where I pulled in iron icons.
就在这里   我要导入 AV 图标
And here, I'm going to import AV icons.
现在所有的这些图标我都有权限使用
Now all of those icons will be available to me as well.
所以我在 iron-icon 里拷贝然后放到显示 av：snooze 的框中
So copy in my iron-icon and drop in one that says av:snooze.
那么任何时候你使用不在默认集合内的集合中的图标
And anytime you're using an icon from a set that is not
只需加个前缀即可
the default set, you're going to need to prefix it
前缀包含集合名称和冒号
with the set name and a colon.
现在当我转回我的编辑器的时候
Now when I hop back into my editor,
你能看到我的安卓图标
you can see I've got my Android icon,
并且我能找到我的 AV snooze 图标
and I've got my AV snooze icon.
现在  你知道我最后想说的事情是
Now, the last thing that I want to do-- as you recall,
我们可以使用自定义属性设置这些元素风格
we can style the elements using these custom properties
比如宽度和高度
for width and height.
那么我再转回我的编辑器
So I'm going to hop back into my editor
创建一个 theme.html 文档
and create a theme.html file.
在文档中  我再创建一个用户风格
And inside of this file, I'm going to create a custom style
属性
property.
这样样式就变成了自定义样式
So style is custom style.
这就有点像是风格菜单
And I can treat this kind of like a style sheet.
我将鼠标选中 iron-icon 元素
So I'll target the iron-icon element.
现在我就能选中这里面的自定义属性
And now I can target the custom properties inside of this.
那么我就要使得这里所有的 iron-icons
So I'm just going to make all iron-icons have
很宽很高 这样它们基本上
a really big width and height so that they're
在很远的距离也能被看见
visible from space, basically.
既然我设置了宽度和高度
So I've set width and height.
我就来导入我的主题文档了
I'm going to import my theme file.
现在我返回我的浏览器并且刷新页面
And now when I go back to my browser and refresh the page,
看这就是我的巨大图标
I've got these ginormous icons.
再次强调  把它们做得这么大是不对的
So again, it's kind of absurd to make them this big.
但是这种图标的属性设置方法
But this way, you can globally set the size
是对你的所有 iron-icons 都适用的
for all of your iron-icons.
或者如果你想通过类来选中它
Or if you wanted to target it by class,
那么你能做上述不同的事情
you can do these different things.
在这个案例中  自定义属性的作用
And in this case, it's not a very huge use
并未完全发挥
of custom properties.
但是我希望能帮助你对自定义属性尽快熟悉
But I want to get you familiar with custom properties.
我希望你们对自定义属性的使用尽快上手
I want to get you comfortable using them
因为我们在将来会更多的使用到它们
because we're going to be using them a lot more in the future.
这就是它的用法
So that about does it.
现在你就领略了当前最新最犀利的
You've now got the latest and greatest info
关于图标如何在 Polymer 1.0 中的使用
on working with icons in Polymer 1.0.
朋友们 以上是本周的全部内容
That's it for this week, folks.
要确定点击那个小小的提交按钮
Be sure to click that little Subscribe button.
再次感谢各位的观看
As always, thank you so much for watching.
我们下次再见
I'll see you next time.
[MUSIC PLAYING]